There's not? Gee, because it sure sounds
like there should be.
(Leslie:)Any aspects of our sexual relationship,
regarding your preferences...
(Leslie:)...your idiosyncrasies, your performance,
are protected by the inherent...
(Leslie:)- ...confidentiality of the bedroom.
- That's all very comforting...
...but I'd like to get on my question now.
- Proceed.
- We are entering the Physics Bowl...
(Leonard:)- ...and we need a fourth.
- No, thanks.
I'm really busy with my like-sign dilepton
supersymmetry search.
Dilepton shmylepton, we need you.
(Sheldon:)Sorry.
(Howard:)Well, we tried.
We'll just have to face Sheldon
mano y mano y mano a mano.
(Leslie:)Wait, you're going up against
Sheldon Cooper?
(Raj:)- Yes.
- That arrogant, misogynistic...
(Leslie:)...doorknob that told me I should abandon
my work with high-energy particles...
...for laundry and childbearing?
(Leonard:)She's in.